Yeah okay so hand over to Sophie thank you so much Sophie thank you so
obviously as you
all know today we're going to be talking about how to set up phone chat and SMS
and I've done
this for a while I've just noticed on mine I haven't had an SMS message in ages
and I've just
noticed the little tick box wasn't ticked so that's really helpful but I've had
loads of phone calls
I switch my phone on when I'm in the day job and sometimes when like I'm in bed
and I'm not
sleeping yet and but I think the benefits of this you don't have to like get
ready you don't have
to put nice clothes on any maker and it's another way to earn as well and you
can take calls whilst
you're on cam if you're not on cam if you're walking down the street some
clients find it really
naughty when you like answer and you're like I'm just in my day job and I'll
pretend like I'm doing
something really professional and I can't like say anything naughty so I'm like
you know you use
code words and whatever and like oh yes that system's the best or whatever and
they're like oh I
want to fuck you so hard and you're like oh yes and that that meeting would
work very well
or whatever it's um can be quite horny for them um or if you just you're just
in your scuffs
around the house it's pretty fun um so I'll get so I'm gonna I'm gonna try and
flip my camera
yes I can do it and just film my laptop screen and if I'm going too quick
please just say something
and slow me down um but obviously we're recording this so I think it'd be good
to go back through
the call and you know pause it when you need to and whatever but I shall turn
around now okay so
obviously on the laptop my tiny little laptop so I've logged in as normal on
that button there
and then go to my details edit mode file all the way across to profile details
this is a phone
chat by the way I'll show you how to set up phone chat first and so you get
onto your
edit profile and it's got all the tabs across the top general personal details
pictures webcam
and phone chat so it's got its own special tab so click on that one sorry sorry
Sophie before
you carry on I'm just thinking well it might be better people are watching it
back if you pin
Sophie's green on the main page have you done that so Sophie's green cocks are
big so it's not
just a little box in the corner so it comes up to you if that makes sense so
people watching
I can see yeah you're right yeah you're right yeah sorry for an interrupt yeah
good idea good idea
and also and also sorry one more thing if before you get to the point where you
have that phone chat
box on your profile because if you haven't done phone chat that that tab is not
going to be there
yet so I just want to say we can do that your mentor can do that or from them
yes let me show
you how to get that on okay yeah thanks so um my details so firstly my details
registration details
mind slow I've heard I've had to hotspot my laptop to my phone because right so
registering details
your name comes up and then all your services down here so I've clicked webcam
work phone chat
SMS content creator and alternative so you want to take your phone chat the
phone chat and SMS
or SMS and save that and that should create the tab shouldn't it yeah thanks
yeah well okay
I've had it on so long I forgot that it was never there before okay so then my
details edit profile
looks profile details and then the tab should be up there so click on that one
so I always have this
ticked direct chat only as in tick yes because to say that disabled should pre-
booked phone chat
some like to do this but I think it's a bit more work for you because um I don
't think you get like
a text message or anything I think you get an AdultWork notification so you
would have to sit
on AdultWork and wait for the notification to come through and it says um you
have a phone
chat booking at this time and you basically get 10 minutes to call the clients
as far as I can
remember um or it might have been a text I haven't done it because I found it
too annoying I'm too
like scatter brains I've missed the text and then I've missed the call and then
you missed the money
basically and if you don't call them within 10 minutes you don't get it and I
think they pre-book
a certain amount of time to save it's one credit a minute they book 10 minutes
but because you're
calling them it's like a manual phone call it's not through AdultWork so you
don't necessarily get
paid by the minute you're just using your minutes your credit whatever and if
they go on and on
and on and if you're not good at wrapping up a call and getting them off the
phone then it doesn't
really work and so I always tick that so they always call me um so which is
this tick box here
offer direct chat so that's just my normal phone number in there and the phone
number we use have
all got because they never see your number they call you I'll show you in a sec
um my price at the
moment is 1.3 credits or the minimum is 0.8 credits like on the camp and maybe
start at that to get
people in calling yeah I'll put my phone chat up and down depending on where I
am what I'm doing
if I'm more busy I'll put the price down if I'm literally just sitting there
doing nothing and
especially if someone's emailed me and I've put all over my profile I love
silent calls I love this
I love that um and I'm quite taboo and naughty so I can ask your question if
anyone can hear me
yes go on all right so I'm looking at it now so I've put direct chat only so
what
where's the price the price is but I don't want you paying to talk to nobody
no you don't pay just click see on my screen tick both those boxes and you won
't be paying
so what do I change then no that's fine the both those boxes are ticked it
looks like
just leave it like that yeah all right let me tell me look at you but I'm
fucking done
all right everyone there's a lot joining again okay thank you um so yeah so I
've got
that this with this space section direct chat settings that's all you need to
do unless
you untick that box and then down here pre-booked phone chat if you really want
to do that you put
your pricing your phone number and you can show your phone number or I think
they get
they yeah they could get your number with you ring them and but obviously if
you use 141
or call blocking and but that should be done so if you go on save and view
and then in your normal bio thing profile bio scroll down to the contact me
and then it should have underneath your webcam bit it should have to phone chat
via direct chat
call this number I used to say click here okay but so the client would
literally pick up their phone
ring that number and then obviously that's my user ID but they'd have a
different user ID they
would enter their user ID on the phone and then enter their PIN and it would
connect to me
and start chatting to the phone call you get is from like an 0208 number and it
says in to
accept a call from AdultWork something something breast one so you just press
one and then it
connects to them hello I'm just on a work call of oh you brought me some
flowers
she's brought me some flowers thank you thank you I'll come down soon I'm just
doing somewhere
okay sorry guys um she's so cute um okay so that should be on and I thought a
good idea maybe if
everyone wants to like later on pair up and ring each other to test it sort of
thing and if you're
in pairs and you know you spend a credit on that person but they'll spend a
credit on this one
yeah all right let me carry on yeah that looks good shan that looks like it's
set up
don't put a little more do then you just wait for the calls
sorry pardon sorry I don't I don't know what I'm doing my camera
all done we turn it back on
there you go go on then you okay okay okay so that was phone chat
any more questions from anyone I also I have one question please yeah so um
when you were on the page where you were set in your price per minute stuff
like that
you had 1.3 but then underneath I've seen it had 0.99 I'm not sure what that
meant if that was
that was for the if they call you um so that that didn't mean anything
basically
but aren't they calling you anyway through our other way or
call so a bit confusable yeah phone chat price and direct chat price
yeah so direct chat is different to pre-book chat so if that was a pre-book but
you don't
use that one and you don't use that okay okay box means no pre-book chat and it
just
okay I tried this before it won't let me put zero in it won't let me change
this
regarding thank you yeah I just once about that 99 was but yeah yeah no I was
trying
to get rid of it I knew it would be confusing um but it's just there it won't
go away
yeah I just didn't see that I said pre-book there but yeah I guess that now
thank you
yeah yeah that's the pre-book section and to use that you would click that and
then it would let
you change yeah let's you change it when it's yeah when you tick that box or
when you untick that
box it let you change it but I personally don't like to use that but obviously
it's
personal preference okay so anything else about are you using my lipstick
it's breaking in that one this um calls last I think two hours isn't it that
you are
they can call in two hours time and you later have to do the same again if you
want to stay longer
say that again sorry the pre-booked no no not pre-book just the normal one like
he's like he showed
is usually sorry just my laundry is coming usually it's like two hours you stay
on isn't it
and later you need to do again it's the same thing yeah sorry I have to wait
for a moment my laundry
yes sorry hi sorry can I just say yeah I've just been trying to do that and it
's been a click say
we kept saying I had a warning um I needed to fix my credits for foam chat you
do actually have
to put a prize in the pre-booked one for that warning to go oh okay well maybe
that's why that
99p won't disappear then possibly because I've just done it and as soon as I
put a price in that one
and saved it it's gone the warning's gone okay good point yeah so obviously you
need
something in that bit to um for it to for it to work um okay so availability if
I remember I
always do this on my phone the availability so I can't remember where it is um
if I log out
and then log back in oh I've got no image oh there it is um it's a bit slow oh
it's just a bit
slow because of the hotspot I don't know the wifi here dq and I never get these
things right I think
I'm gonna move up there we go um oh I'm already available so it didn't pop up
but usually when
you log in the screen pops up and says are you available um but I will try and
follow me
it's by in my details and then availability so yeah if that's just spotted it
thank you Kelsey
my details scroll down to availability direct available now direct cam
availability and direct
camshoe schedule so you just click available now and then my status I am
available for phone chat
bookings um I better switch that off actually because I'll make it case
something interrupts so
that's for your phone chat and then if your Twitter is linked you can click
that and it will put a
little post up for you on Twitter so update that and that should be it for
phone chats anymore
questions or notes or anything hi I um I've got a question I'm Ruby
hi thank you so much for showing us all that cassia before she left she said
something about
a two-hour limit do we have to restart and come back again yes yes that was
what I was going to do
so the availability so once you are on my details page um the availability
switches itself off
after two hours if you um get um one of the called SMS alerts from a w then it
will text you saying
your available now stasis has been changed so and I used to be able to text it
back you just text
it back with the code it's like oh npc it tells you in the text what to text
back but that doesn't
work for me anymore I think it's because of my phone settings um but you just
have to go back on
and make yourself available then it just switches itself off
so let me click that now it's probably just being slow yeah it's just being
slow
um but yeah it does switch itself off after two hours so you have to keep an
eye on it but if you
put it on about you know two o'clock then you you may you could set an alarm
for ten to four
you know set another alarm for ten to six and whatever or you can go on it
manually
and just say I'm not available like if you've noticed if you think about after
an hour or whatever
you just go oh well I'm not available oh yes I'm available and I think that
restarts the two hours
as well um so I'll switch that off for now does that help Ruby thank you very
much thank you
okay fabulous okay anything else before we move on to us mass
if you have one question please so see yeah so um one of one of the members is
trying to set
up her phone chat and she's putting an earphone number because I think yet you
do you have to verify
your phone number fair is that right yeah I think they text you yeah and you
text back with the code
yeah for the reason it's just not coming up throughout like did you have to put
in your phone provider
on a drop-down list and click what phone provider you are like you know whether
you would throw
the phone or eat it or whatever else or was it too long ago now that you don't
remember
probably yeah I honestly can't remember sorry I have that I have set my own up
I've got a question
let me ask because I I'm sorry I don't know if I unmuted or if I was on no go
on Shanna can you
ask all right thank you just a quick one because more time when I turn on my
team I have it tell me
that you've just been like I have to put a numbering or something and a doubt
like that I send a text
to wear so I don't send that part it would give me up five numbers eight so I'm
going to talk with
this that and then sometimes even if I turn it on it puts me on so I don't get
that so I just
kick them or do I have to sign back in that's that's all right there we go that
's probably what
George has just mentioned you probably have to I was just trying to put on it
like I don't get that
myself it might be the availability thing that Sophie's just said it might be
that you get an
a text to say that it's made you unavailable so you just need to click on
availability there
and make yourself available like Sophie just showed yeah or Kirsty's just said
if you go to my details
and mobile activation so let's have a look at that okay yeah current status
your mobile has been
verified you like to remove or change and abuse your edit profile either so
obviously I don't know
how to verify from now and various parts of this site will send you SMS
messages depending on your
number type and the activities you perform you do booking requests or send by
SMS members in the
UK will almost certainly need to contact their network operator and perform age
verification
before being able to take part in the site's SMS functionality yeah yeah okay
your your network
provider sometimes has a block on age sometimes has an age restriction thing
don't they so I know
a lot of people when I've set it up for them they've had to contact their
provider to say that they
are over 18 and so it doesn't want but what George what were you saying I don't
I don't know if you
finish your question that you were saying what were you saying about the having
to ask what their
provider was yeah I think because um for some reason you get like when you get
the text message to say
text back with this code to verify your age or whatever it is she was texting
back with the code
but it just was not accepting like it wasn't working on other words that she
was verified I don't know
if she's having some troubles but I'm going to set up my own phone number and
take myself with the
process because then she's going to socially it's probably change as we know
they change things all
the time so I'll take myself through the process and see how it works because
yeah I don't think
yeah I think you'll have the answer for me because it's all of the same
can I ask one more thing then go on because sometimes I'll get a text and like
I've been disconnected
but when I do text chat I get paid all right so is it when they're turning off
is it them turning
it off that is just simple because sometimes I look at my phone like you've
just been disconnected
why and then text this message it's weird it's disconnected from sms yeah from
um from from AW yeah
just just a bunch I can be online but it doesn't disconnect my whole phone I'm
verified in my number run so if the phone me or text me it should work
sometimes it just slow though
okay well shall I start the bit on sms now then well I've been learning that
now
I'm just listening to you look cool all right I think I think if you go just
carry on yeah carry on
I think if you've got if you've got questions about like that sort of thing
maybe we can use
those after shan just so we can get there yeah because that was all about phone
chat shan so
that's done now and then now I'll move on to sms so hopefully I can answer your
questions there
I will try thank you thank you thank you right so back into your normal login
my details edit profile profile details so back onto this normal page so sms
doesn't have its own tab um it's in general so it's in your contact details
right on the first
page of your profile the edit um profile bit so general contact details and
then all your bits
and bobs and then this tick box needs to be ticked accept sms via AdultWork
and then my preferred
contact method is to write sms texts um obviously you can do your AW email or a
direct chat call
or because you get it instantly and you get money pair text I prefer that not
that anyone's
been using it because they didn't have that box ticked for some reason um so
scroll right down
and save and view and then so in your normal profile page and this is what the
client would say
profile gallery private gallery movies etc and then your bio etc so you scroll
down and under that
is the contact me so if you have a look at your own page once you've ticked
that box I think as far
as I can remember it just shows up with this box once you've verified your
phone number
and everything via that text message thing there should just be a box here so
to send me an SMS
enter your message here and then it even says preferred contact methods and
then this box there
you just type whatever you want or they type whatever they want and then click
send now um
and unfortunately you only get half a credit per message that you send back so
it's annoying
when you miss a text but I think you still do get a credit even if you text
them back
like a day later or whatever because you get paid via the text that you send
back
if they text you don't be thinking oh I've just been paid there no you have to
text them back
so while sometimes you get little essays off them and it'll send two text
messages
and it'll send two texts because it's so long but if you just text them back a
few word answers
like that sounds fun and then they'll send you another little essay and you're
like oh tell me
more and you get them paid half a credit for like three words and again you can
sit on the
bus you can sit in work sit in birds um you know you just need your phone on
loud and you receive
texts and I think that is it because obviously it has been a while since I
first set this up and
I've only just noticed today that a lot of little tick box wasn't ticked for me
so hopefully now
it will be ticked um and of course as we said the registration details
make sure the SMS chat is ticked I think that's the most important thing and
then that other
text tick box and your verification bot whoever wants to set this up who hasn't
set up before
we can just sort of get into pairs and text everyone I mean if just to make it
fair kind
of thing of one person is texting everyone they'll get charged but if we sort
of pair up and do it
and I don't mind pairing up with someone because I want to check that my SMS is
working as well
um and even if we don't text each other back so then we won't take credits kind
of thing I think
it costs the client's one credit to send the first text message and then what
the site must take
that I think and then we get half a credit pair um pair message we send back
and also about phone
chat they don't get to call you they can't call you unless they have minimum of
five minutes worth
of credits so if it's a credit a minute they need five credits before they can
even call you
um and obviously a lot of them run out of credit but a lot of them hang off
after one two minutes
so you can't predict it you can't you know you you just try and make them stay
um I just start
talking worse and worse can't say too much has got little ears next to me but
you know just make
the conversation more and more intriguing and then they're like oh really like
yeah and this and this
and just try and keep them going um any more questions about SMS
hi so we have one question please if that's okay
you said that when the client um texted you across them one credit but then
you don't receive that you receive it when you text back you receive half a
credit
can you just text back numerous textors people's building of the credit or is
it just one text back
if you text them again then you don't get paid for it it comes up saying the
shoes hasn't received this message you haven't you just haven't haven't no no
no kind of thing
but yeah good question because oh that might be the case but I thought that
just the butter
yeah otherwise you've got to respond to their text
yes you've got to respond to their text they start it so they send you the
first text
and then you text back get paid because I tend it's ping ping ping yeah yeah
you could sit there all
day just rinsing them sending them 50 text messages an hour not be nice yeah it
would favour yeah
but that's it anything else um would you say that you're like you've got very
busy with text
and phone calls obviously this is something I've never done so I'm not sure how
often
it would come through do you get a last pay day or pay week it's not
necessarily busy but it's
I think of it as free money because you don't have to sit there and get ready
whatever
um one of the girls says she gets busy from like seven in the morning um I'm
never ever up at that
time so but I tend to um get busy after literally after my bed time which is
annoying um if I
accidentally leave my phone chat on I'll start getting calls after 11 at night
and then a lot of
them are after 12 and if you put it on your um I update my oh this is so so I
update my tagline
every time I'm online I think it's in personal details when it's in general I'm
used to the mobile
site sorry but um new tagline so I think it's gone yeah personal details yeah
then this is one
on direct comes it has yeah you mean the one on type I come setting it's like
the same one as the
no it's a different one there I never really changed I want to change this one
your summary
shows up on your family yeah you know so I I just changed a few words um when I
've put on mine I'm
amazing at silent calls to be real play jay why humiliation could go on much
more not either better
and then like so last night I added this to the end of it I'm on the phone
tonight to call me now
um and then I think I've got more details in my bio just in case they read it
which they never do
really but occasionally I'll get an email going on while your profile sounds
amazing
can we talk about this and this and I'm like yeah about what time and sometimes
they take days to
email you back um and you've got like an email conversation going for a bit but
when they've got
good feedback um I I do take the time to email them because it's almost like a
text but it's like
a free text and if I miss their emails by a day or whatever I always make a
point of saying
text me instead I'll get it instantly and then we can have a chat about what
you want and then
you can ring me instantly and it's much more quick for one to the better way
they just you know what
I mean it's like texting somebody can you call me now yeah I can call you now
sound but if on an email
obviously you have to pay to get notifications for the emails and I'm just a
chief skater don't like
to pay anything before avenge anything so I'll just but I do take the time to
email them back
and they'll send you big long scenarios um if they want a silent call so I'll
screenshot that
and I'll email them back and say you know and I don't expect in a couple of
calls I'll say cough
when I answer because they literally want to be silenced they don't want to be
heard at all by
anyone around them so they cough and then I'll say they're username and then
they cough again
to confirm that it's them then I go through my screenshots find their um
scenario that they
want is and just just go wild basically um and take it as far as I can and
usually every email
stage you have any limits to have any death start and then they all say no but
I soon find them
because they're full fannies um but yeah any more questions you know when you
see people um
you see people featuring a them for sms or direct I am how do you do that
feature because there's
not many featuring you're in the day and it'd be ideal for me to wake up from
home like so
so I don't know about this oh right okay I don't I don't spend anything to
feature
all right okay I think you can see it from the my details page can't you um if
I'm right
Georgia you've gone to my details and scroll down to the bottom um speak is it
on the feature
please do your profile speak to your profile I think it will bring up options
like direct cam
direct chat all right okay I think direct cam position yeah business builds are
in profile
promotion right feet to your profile do you mind my boyfriend's just walked in
completely naked now
he's like look at me um right feature your profile direct um direct chat oh
yeah so similar to direct
cam you bid your prices per hour all right but I'm not sure about sms if we
click on sms or yeah
it doesn't seem to be an sms of the day well okay you'll just feature on that
page then
will you if you set up for sms then yeah yeah apparently they're featured oh no
these are featured
that it was right there um I've just found on it once you're going you um my
details if you go onto
the page where it shows all the purple things then Dan here at the bottom
you can click uh feature in oh sorry you can't see it so you click profile
feature in
yeah and then there is a selection where you can change it to um webcam oh that
's brilliant
oh great oh fast case that way isn't it for the full day
oh right oh if it's all backwards and stuff yeah no don't worry I just I can't
find that on the
and so it's on the right side of the screen right hand side and the right hand
side so go
scroll down and then featuring yes and you can do sms go and add me using 360
those ones are for
the full yeah put planning in advance perfect yeah yeah this is featuring
rather than position
isn't it right sms that's what I do I thought that you can do it elsewhere in
chat sms oh wow
amazing yeah that's so useful wonderful oh and it's only 2.5 credits to feature
for tomorrow and then in fact every day for the full day that's not going to be
good if you were in
if you were in work or whatever obviously yeah if you can if you can
sorry listen to you everyone can hear you oh and now he's got the hair dryer on
thanks love
oh my days this has only been recorded for everybody so professional um I've
lost me training
thought now that's okay thank you okay she's like the AdultWork nerd if she if
she doesn't know
it's not going to go in should I think you've read every single word on this
website
I think we're just trying to go through everything yeah that's fast but it's
fast I know it is
amazing and so yeah so see when they text you when they text they don't see a
number also right
just the what happens they don't see it when they call no yeah okay you do that
one and where's
the file just go through like a different number the thing from the profile isn
't the text they
text you through the website so they could sit on this but then they do it from
their phone as well
and then they just apply the first initial text yeah exactly the first initial
text they write in
this box um obviously it won't let me text myself but send that now your
credits account will be
debits is one credit and your message will be sent to receive click okay oh
maybe you can text yourself
oh you cannot put them in the cell nevermind but yeah so obviously they get
that and then they must
receive a text back um but it pops up on your phone you get two messages one
will say you have
received an SMS message from user blah blah blah and then the message from then
comes through
and I think that might be two separate numbers job so you need to reply to
their message
and then that's when you get paid for it and then it looks like a normal text
okay
just right away between the two half yeah how long do you find the text for
just this very
oh some of them will text a few texts a night um some of them will send one
long dirty text then
you text back and you never hear from them again um so just like they wind
themselves off
they you know you know what I mean they wind themselves up just writing the
stuff and then like
you text them one thing and then they must just go whoo that's it then that's
all they need um nice
and cheap for them yeah well it all adds up you know what I mean of course yeah
it's only half
of credit so it's only about what 25 30 pay yeah and um if you're texting a
couple of people at once
as well as phone calls as well as calm it's just it just bumps it off yeah adds
a few extra I feel
like it would be really good for keeping in touch with your regulars as well
like if even if you do
in like gfb then it's a good way because they're always on the end there just
say oh you can text
me through the site or if you've done it you could be like I want to know that
you've not touched
tomorrow so yeah message me at this time and this time right I've done that
before yeah I've done
that before and said well you need to text me regular updates I'll be like you
need to text me
regular updates what you're doing what you're not doing and all that kind of
thing um yeah just
just bumps up the income can be good uh thank you so much Sophie that was so
that was so good
and Kirsty as well thank you so much yeah I love it yeah thank you Sophie that
was great I really
appreciate it I know it now yeah yes good we'll get set in it up and then um
someone text me please I'll
text you back I'll text you through the site that with me and me but you know I
actually
have to realise I don't know if we're going to be able to text each other
because I know we can't
come each other because we're all in the same group I've tried to do it before
what I've come
people are in the same group just to check things and they say you can't come
with this person because
you're in the same group group this was about a year ago and as we know they
changed things often
so we'll try it but we can't put under the same group I don't know if we can
what's okay I went into free with Catherine before
I've not tried to do no text to have it or anything I think it's just working
okay
yeah they'll um they'll want to take the the their court so I'm sure they'll
let anyone
come with anyone yeah you think you never used to be able to come in people in
the same group
like if you're a user you're sat like at the way we are in where clusters
offering services not
speaking services you know like I wasn't allowed to come with the same offering
service to people
in the same group but like I said that was a year or so ago so maybe it's
different but we'll try
the text in anyway I've gone on someone's free before just to check it out just
to look just to
see what it looks like from the client's point of view yeah it might just be
free I think it might
just be free or if we can't text each other I'm sure one of us has got a sub
that we can just
give a list of profiles still and they can text them that's a good idea yeah
fab will hopefully I'll get some now I've ticked the right box again but yeah
we can all just keep
in touch and just say what what we've received and if it's working and go from
there I'm happy to
keep helping in the group if anyone's got any problem as best as can anyway
thank you so much
thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you very much it was nice to see
you all as well
yeah it's lovely to see everyone have a lovely day girlies too thank you thank
you
thanks everyone see ya thank you